Finding Aid for the Alumni Relations Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Alumni and Development
  - National Development Committee - Vanderbilt University, John Poindexter (Box 2720, Folder 31)
  - Nursing School, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 1)
  - Plough, Abe, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 3)
  - Poindexter - Personal, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 4)
  - Politics Center - Robert J. Bird Proposal, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 5)
  - Position Papers - 1973, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 6)
  - Position Papers - 1973, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 7)
  - Report on a Study of Voluntary Support Resources and Potential and a Proposed Plan of Action, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 8)
  - Reports from Various Teams, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 9)
  - Southeastern Council of Foundations, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 10)
  - Stallworth Rehabilitation Planning, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 11)
  - T. Rowe Price, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 12)
  - Task Force on the Stadium Question - Emmett B. Fields, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 13)
  - Tennessee Independent Colleges Fund, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 14)
  - Tennessee Independent Colleges Fund, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 15)
  - University Divinity Schools: A Report on Ecclesiastically Independent Theological Education, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 16)
  - Wills and Trusts, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 17)
  - Wilson, Vernon, John Poindexter (Box 2721, Folder 18)
  - Administration - Alumni and Development - 1965-1969, Don Elliott (Box 2721, Folder 19)
  - Administration - Alumni and Development - 1967-1968, Don Elliott (Box 2721, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Association By-Laws, Don Elliott (Box 2721, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Association Committee on Regulations - 1951-1967, Don Elliott (Box 2721, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Association Program, Don Elliott (Box 2721, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Board Communications, Don Elliott (Box 2721, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Questionnaire, Don Elliott (Box 2721, Folder 25)
  - Associates, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 1)
  - Associates Program - Correspondence, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 2)
  - Associates Program - Nashville Special People, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 3)
  - Associates Program - Original Lists - 1, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 4)
  - Associates Program - Original Lists - 2, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 5)
  - Associates Program - Original Lists - 3, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 6)
  - Associates Program - Original Lists - 4, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 7)
  - Associates Program - Original Lists - 5, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 8)
  - Associates Program - Preliminary Lists - January, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 9)
  - Associates Program - Preliminary Lists - January, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 10)
  - Associates Program - Preliminary Lists - June, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 11)
  - Associates Program - Special Lists - February, 1964, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 12)
  - Associates Program - Vanderbilt University Associates, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 13)
  - Branscomb Letter, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 14)
  - Brief Analysis of Contributions, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 15)
  - Cabinet Meetings, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 16)
  - Campus Campaign, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 17)
  - Central Files, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 18)
  - Chancellor Heard's Inauguration (Folder 1 of 3), Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 19)
  - Chancellor Heard's Inauguration (Folder 2 of 3), Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 20)
  - Chancellor Heard's Inauguration (Folder 3 of 3), Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 21)
  - Chancellor Heard's Inauguration - Invitations, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Material, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 23)
  - Communications Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 24)
  - Communications Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 25)
  - Communications Committee - John Dixon, Don Elliott (Box 2722, Folder 26)
  - Computer, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 1)
  - Computer Applications, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 2)
  - Computer Center, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 3)
  - Computer Center, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 4)
  - Computer Center, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 5)
  - Computer Center - MacLeod Report, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 6)
  - Computer Designs for Alumni and Development, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 7)
  - Computer Notes, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 8)
  - Computer Program, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 9)
  - Computer Program, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 10)
  - Computer Program - Alumni Records Analysis and Conversion Records Proposals, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 11)
  - Computer Program - Data Processing Program, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 12)
  - Computer Program - General Files on Program, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 13)
  - Consecutive Years Contributing, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - Don Elliott - Don Giffin, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - John Beasley - Don Giffin, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 16)
  - Development Staff Meetings, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 17)
  - Gift Summaries, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 18)
  - Gift Summaries, January - May, 1964, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 19)
  - Gift Summaries, June - December, 1964, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 20)
  - Gift Summaries, Don Elliott (Box 2723, Folder 21)
  - Gift Summaries, January - April, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 1)
  - Gift Summaries, May - September, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 2)
  - Gift Summaries, April - December, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 3)
  - Gift Summaries, January - April, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 4)
  - Gift Summaries, May - August, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 5)
  - Gift Summaries, September - December, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 6)
  - Gifts - Daily and Weekly Reports, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 7)
  - Goals and Objectives, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 8)
  - Guide to Programs and Activities, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 9)
  - Harold H. Everett's A.C.T. Plan, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 10)
  - IBM (International Business Machine), Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 11)
  - Medical School Alumni Program, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 12)
  - Movie Program, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 14)
  - News Bureau Program, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 15)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - August, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 16)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - September, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 17)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - October, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 18)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - November, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 19)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - December, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 20)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - January, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 21)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - February, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 22)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - March, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 23)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - April, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 24)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - May, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 25)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - June, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 26)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - July, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 27)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - August, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 28)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - September, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 29)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - October, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 30)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - November, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 31)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - December, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 32)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - January - February, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 33)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - March, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 34)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - April, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 35)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - May, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 36)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - June, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 37)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - July, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 38)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - August, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 39)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - September, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 40)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - October, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 41)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - November, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 42)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - December, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 43)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - January, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 44)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - February, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 45)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - March, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 46)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - April, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 47)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - May, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 48)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - June, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2724, Folder 49)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - July, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 1)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - August, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 2)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - September, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 3)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - October, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 4)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - November, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 5)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - December, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 6)
  - News Bureau Program - News Releases - January, 1969, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 7)
  - News Clippings and Releases, 1965-1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 8)
  - Outstanding Young Women of America, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 9)
  - Patent Planning Committee Program, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 10)
  - Patients' Program, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 11)
  - Planning Session - July 14, 1965, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 12)
  - Policy and Procedures, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 13)
  - Policy and Procedures, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 14)
  - Policy and Procedures, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 15)
  - Policy and Procedures, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 16)
  - Policy and Procedures, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 17)
  - Policy and Procedures - Race Relations, Integration, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 18)
  - Policy and Procedures - Subfile on Academic Freedom, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 19)
  - President Kennedy's Visit, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 20)
  - Reference Books Program, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 21)
  - Report Breakfasts - Agenda - February 14, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 22)
  - Report Breakfasts - Assignment Lists - February 14, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 23)
  - Report Breakfasts - Invitation List - February 14, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 24)
  - Report Breakfasts - Minutes - February 14, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 25)
  - Report Breakfasts - Agenda - January 24, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 26)
  - Report Breakfasts - Assignment Lists - January 24, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 27)
  - Report Breakfasts - Invitation List - January 24, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 28)
  - Report Breakfasts - Minutes - January 24, 1967, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 29)
  - Report Breakfasts - Agenda - December 20, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 30)
  - Report Breakfasts - Assignment Lists - December 20, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 31)
  - Report Breakfasts - Invitation List - December 20, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 32)
  - Report Breakfasts - Minutes - December 20, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 33)
  - Report Breakfasts - Agenda - December 5, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 34)
  - Report Breakfasts - Assignment Lists - December 5, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 35)
  - Report Breakfasts - Invitation List - December 5, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 36)
  - Report Breakfasts - Minutes - December 5, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 37)
  - Report Breakfasts - Agenda - January 10, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 38)
  - Report Breakfasts - Assignment Lists - January 10, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 39)
  - Report Breakfasts - Invitation List - January 10, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 40)
  - Report Breakfasts - Minutes - January 10, 1966, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 41)
  - Report to the Chancellor - Development and Alumni Affairs, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 42)
  - Reports on Gifts (Folder 1 of 2), Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 43)
  - Reports on Gifts (Folder 2 of 2), Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 44)
  - Science Center Dedication, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 45)
  - Self Study Program, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 46)
  - Special Prospects Program - Bahnsen, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 47)
  - Special Prospects Program - Cultivation Letters Program, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 48)
  - Special Prospects Program - Special Prospects and Lists, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 49)
  - Special Prospects Program - VIP Program, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 50)
  - Special Prospects Program - VIP Program: Sloan's Salutations, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 51)
  - Special Prospects Program - Arizona, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 52)
  - Special Prospects Program - Florida, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 53)
  - Special Prospects Program - Louisiana, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 54)
  - Special Prospects Program - Southern California, Don Elliott (Box 2725, Folder 55)
  - Sponsored Research Reports, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 1)
  - Suggestions to Vanderbilt Alumni and to Other Individuals, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 2)
  - Summer Planning Sessions, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 3)
  - Telephone Campaign, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 4)
  - Thirty Million Campaign, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 5)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Vanderbilt University Expenditures, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 6)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Gift Handling, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 7)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Law School, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 8)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Library, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 9)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Material for Campaign, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 10)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Middle Tennessee, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 11)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - National Development Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 12)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - New Goals and New Objectives, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 13)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Newspaper Clippings, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 14)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Pamphlets, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 15)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Solicitation, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 16)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Special Prospects and Project Assignments, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 17)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - Tax Information, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 18)
  - Thirty Million Campaign - VIP Information Sheets, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 19)
  - Vanderbilt Alumni Association, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 20)
  - Vanderbilt University Club Meetings, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 21)
  - Vice-Chancellor William Force, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 22)
  - Visit of Fred Robie, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 23)
  - Wages, Prices, Profits and Productivity, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 24)
  - Wills, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 25)
  - W. S. Ponton - Mailing List, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 26)
  - Annual Report - Graduate School of Management, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 27)
  - Annual Reports of Deans to Board of Trust, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 28)
  - Medical Center Building Plan, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 29)
  - Nashville University Center Council Cooperative Study, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 30)
  - Profile of Vanderbilt University - Volume 2 - Ford Foundation, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 31)
  - Progress Report of College and University Campaigns - December, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 32)
  - Tax Advantages of a Gift to Vanderbilt, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 33)
  - Vanderbilt Hospital - Staff Members and Medical Alumni, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 34)
  - Vanderbilt Medical Center Report, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 35)
  - Vanderbilt Medical Center Report, Spring 1970; Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 36)
  - Volunteers for Vanderbilt, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 37)
  - What's It All For?, Don Elliott (Box 2726, Folder 38)
  - Development Foundation - Correspondence, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 1)
  - Development Foundation - Correspondence, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 2)
  - Development Foundation - Correspondence, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 3)
  - Development Foundation - Correspondence, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 4)
  - Development Foundation - Kersting Brown and Company, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 5)
  - Development Foundation - Kersting Brown and Company - Campaign Directives (Folder 1 of 2), Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 6)
  - Development Foundation - Kersting Brown and Company - Campaign Directives (Folder 2 of 2), Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 7)
  - Development Foundation - Birmingham, Alabama, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 8)
  - Development Foundation - Birmingham Alumni Club, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 9)
  - Development Foundation - Houston, Texas, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 10)
  - Development Foundation - New York City, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 11)
  - Development Foundation - Chattanooga, Tennessee, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 12)
  - Development Foundation - Dallas, Texas, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 13)
  - Development Foundation - Miami, Florida, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 14)
  - Development Foundation - Washington Alumni Club, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 15)
  - Development Foundation - Tampa, Florida, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 16)
  - Development Foundation - Paducah Alumni Club, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 17)
  - Development Foundation - Jackson, Mississippi, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 18)
  - Development Foundation - Jackson, Tennessee, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 19)
  - Development Foundation - Pensacola, Florida, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 20)
  - Development Foundation - Atlanta Vanderbilt Club, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 21)
  - Nashville Business Campaign - Sample Book, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 22)
  - Nashville Business Campaign - Sample Book, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 23)
  - Class Agents Program - Letter 1 - October, 1964, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 24)
  - Class Agents Program - Letter 2 - Fall, 1964, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 25)
  - Class Agents Program - Letter 3 - December, 1964, Don Elliott (Box 2727, Folder 26)
  - Class Agents Program - VIP Letters, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 1)
  - Class Agents Program - Letters, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 2)
  - Class Agents Program - Letters, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 3)
  - Class Agents Program - Letters, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 4)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 5)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 6)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 7)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 8)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 9)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 10)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 11)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2728, Folder 12)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 1)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 2)
  - Fund Raising Mailing Material, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Business Campaign, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 4)
  - Vanderbilt Calling - Fund Raising Material, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 5)
  - Administration of the University, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 6)
  - Administration of Vanderbilt University, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Association, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 8)
  - Architects and Contractors, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 9)
  - Archives Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 12)
  - Budget Speech - Background Material for Job Descriptions, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 13)
  - Building - Vanderbilt University, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 14)
  - Bachelor of Ugliness, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 15)
  - Centennial of Vanderbilt, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 16)
  - Class Agents - Vanderbily, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 17)
  - Contact - October 15, 1968, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 18)
  - Critical Path Method, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Meetings - Agendas, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 20)
  - Dean's Meetings - Minutes, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 21)
  - Development Office - Assistance to Students, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 22)
  - Development Office - Promotional Handbook, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 23)
  - Dixon Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2729, Folder 25)
  - Facts About Vanderbilt - Enrollment Figures, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 1)
  - Finance Committee, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 2)
  - Hustler, Vanderbilt, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 3)
  - Joint University and Civic Center for the Performing Arts, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 4)
  - Joint University Libraries (Contains Photographs), Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 5)
  - Living Endowment, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 6)
  - Mace - Proposed Design for Vanderbilt, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 7)
  - Master Plan for Vanderbilt, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 8)
  - Nashville Business Campaign, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 9)
  - Nashville Business Campaign, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Business Campaign - Vice-Chairmen Commodore's Log, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Business Solicitation, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 12)
  - National Advisory Group, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 13)
  - News Bureau, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 14)
  - Office of Development and Alumni Affairs Report - To Chancellor, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 15)
  - Patent Policy, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 16)
  - Performing Arts Center, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 17)
  - Planning Study, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 18)
  - Plaques, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 19)
  - Project Equality, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 20)
  - Projected University Needs, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 21)
  - Public Relations - News Bureau, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 22)
  - Purdy's (Rob Roy) List of Questions, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 23)
  - Resolutions, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 24)
  - Restricted Funds Budgets, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 25)
  - Role of Alumni and Gift Figures, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 26)
  - Sarratt's Fiftieth Year, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 27)
  - Senate Meetings, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 28)
  - Social Relevance - Proposal, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 29)
  - Speeches - Branscomb, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 30)
  - Speeches - Don Elliott, Don Elliott (Box 2730, Folder 31)
  - Speeches - Don Elliott, Don Elliott (Box 2731, Folder 1)
  - Speeches - Miscellaneous Vanderbilt, Don Elliott (Box 2731, Folder 2)